# David Braga Vieira

Junior Full Stack Software Developer

Auckland, New Zealand **021 140 6539** 

E bragav.david@gmail.com

david-braga

。 <u>David Braga V.</u>

#### **ABOUT ME**

Originally from Brazil, I have been living in and loving Aotearoa for almost 9 years now.

I have a passion for learning and since I started my first online HTML and CSS courses in 2019 I haven't stopped. I had decided to change my career but knew I had to work hard so I worked full time during the week and studied at nights and during the weekends.

Recently, I have completed a Software Development Bootcamp and after this life changing experience I am a Web Developer keen to continue evolving and learning.

I am an active person who enjoys many kinds of sports and outdoor activities in my free time.

I have a background in Hospitality which gave me the ability to work well under pressure and great Interpersonal Skills. It also helped me improve my attention to details.

I also worked as an abseiler doing building maintenance and this experience taught me the importance of working in a team and meeting deadlines.

### EXPERIENCE

### Enspiral Dev Academy, Remote — Apprenticeship

AUG 2021 - DEC 2021

- Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp.
- More than 700 hours coding on multiple projects in a team environment following Agile principles replicating real life conditions.

### **CitySide Properties Ltd,** Auckland — Height Technician/ Team leader

JUN 2017 - AUG 2021

- General building maintenance via abseil.
- Always working in teams following safety standards and making sure the jobs were done on time.

#### SKILLS

Teamplayer

Attention to detail

Enthusiastic

Self-Motivated

#### **TECHNOLOGY**

HTML

**CSS** 

Javascript

Node Js.

GitHub

ReactJs

Redux

ExpressJs

### LANGUAGES

Portuguese

English

Spanish

# **Swiss Belsuites Victoria Park**, Auckland — Hotel Receptionist

FEB 2017 - JUN 2017

 Responsible for greeting and checking- in and checkingout guests, liaising with other departments, making bookings, night auditing and answering phone calls and replying to emails.

### **Black Sheep Backpackers**, Queentown — Front Desk

DEC 2014 - DEC 2016

• Check-in and check-out of guests, make bookings, liaise with the Director and the Housekeeping team.

#### **EDUCATION**

# **Enspiral Dev Academy,** Auckland, NZ — Full Stack Web Development Certificate

AUG 2021 - DEC 2021

# **Crown Institute,** Auckland, NZ — Travel and Tourism Diploma

FEB 2013 - JUN 2013

## **IESB - Higher Education Institute of Brasilia,** Brasilia, BR —

Travel and Tourism Bachelor Degree

FEB 2000 - DEC 2004

### **REFERENCES**

Available upon request.